Our first task, starting with the mini-project that you worked on last lesson,
第一个任务是扩展上节课处理的迷你项目
is extended by way of deploying it.
并部署该项目
To follow along, navigate to the SageMaker deployment folder,
要跟着操作 请打开 sagemaker-deployment 文件夹
and then into the tutorials folder,
然后进入 Tutorials 文件夹
and open up the IMDB Sentiment Analysis XGBoost-Web-App Notebook.
打开 IMDB Sentiment Analysis - XGBoost - Web App Notebook
As in the mini-project,
和迷你项目一样
we will start by downloading the data,
首先下载数据
and then doing a little bit of processing.
然后稍微处理数据
So, we start by reading it in.
我们将首先读取数据
If you remember from the mini-project,
在迷你项目中
one of the ways that we converted our views to a list of
将影评转换成字词列表的一种方式是
words was to use Beautiful Soup and NLTK.
使用 BeautifulSoup 和 nltk
We use Beautiful Soup in order to remove any HTML formatting that may have appeared,
我们使用 BeautifulSoup 删除所有的 HTML 格式标记
and we use NLTK to stem the words.
并使用 nltk 词干化字词
Here, we're going to take a bit of a more simplistic approach,
我们将简单处理下
and we're just going to remove any punctuation,
删除影评中的所有标点符号
and any HTML formatting that will appear in our reviews,
以及 HTML 格式标记
and we're just going to do that by using the Python three regular expression module.
我们将使用 Python 3 的正则表达式模块
There's a reason that we've chosen to simplify this method quite a bit and
选择简化此过程的原因是
it has to do with some of the technology that we'll use later.
稍后会用到一些技术
In particular, this makes using Lambda much easier.
这样会使 Lambda 用起来更轻松
So, how does this method work?
这个方法的原理是什么？
Well, suppose we start with this review right here, as you can see,
假设有这样一段影评
there is some HTML formatting,
其中有一些 HTML 格式标记
and we have some punctuation here and here.
这里和这里有些标点
So, review to words,
调用 review_to_words()
we'll then clean that up,
会清理这些标记和标点
and what we're left with is a cleaned version of the review.
生成整洁版本的影评
So, now what we'd like to do is do that to each of the reviews in our data set.
下面对数据集中的每条影评都这么处理
Now, that's done, we need to take our clean reviews,
清理完毕后
and we're going to encode them using Bag-Of-Words.
我们将使用词袋编码整洁的影评
What that means is that we are going to look at all of the reviews in our training set,
即查看训练集中的所有影评
and then we will collect the most frequently appearing words,
然后收集最常出现的字词
and then we will encode each review as a vector,
将每条影评表示成一个向量
where each entry in the vector,
向量中的每项会告诉我们
tells us the number of times that particular word appears in our review.
特定字词出现在影评中的次数
Notice that the vocabulary size that we use here is 5,000,
注意 我们使用的词汇表大小是 5,000
which means that we are only going to track the top
所以我们将仅跟踪训练集中
5,000 most occurring words in our training set.
出现频率在前 5,000 的字词
What that means is,
意思是
once we have encoded a review using the Bag-Of-Words approach,
使用词袋方法编码影评后
we should end up with a vector which has length 5,000, which we do.
获得的向量长度应该为 5,000 我们的长度的确是 5,000
Next we need to move on to uploading our datasets to S3,
接下来需要将数据集上传到 S3
and we do that in this standard way.
我们按照标准方式上传
First, we will split our training set up into a validation and training set.
首先 将训练集拆分为验证集和训练集
Next we will save the test training and validation sets to disk using Pandas,
接着使用 Pandas 将测试 训练和验证集保存到磁盘上
and to save a little bit of memory,
为了节省内存
we will set the variables that held onto our Panda's dataframes to none.
我们将存储 Panda dataframe 的变量设为 none
Keep in mind that the Notebook Instance that you are likely to be using,
注意 我们使用的 Notebook 实例
does not have a lot of RAM available.
并没有多少内存
So, if we just sort of let
如果不再使用这些 dataframe
these dataframes hang around even though we don't need them anymore,
但是还留着
we could end up running out of memory which can lead
可能会耗尽内存
to some sometimes difficult to diagnose issues.
并导致有时候难以诊断的问题
Once that's done, we're going to use
操作完毕后
the SageMaker upload data method to upload our test validation and training sets to S3.
我们将使用 SageMaker upload_data 方法将验证集和训练集上传到 S3
Next step, we create an XGBoost model,
接着创建一个 XGBoost 模型
the same way that you did in the mini-project,
和在迷你项目中的步骤一样
and then we fit the model.
然后拟合模型
Now, that the model is fit, we can go ahead and test it by creating a transformer object,
拟合模型后 创建一个 transformer 对象来测试模型
and then creating a transform job on
然后创建转换作业并在测试数据上运行
our test header to make sure that our model is working as we expect it to.
确保模型的运行效果能达到预期
Once the back-transform job is done,
转换作业运行完毕后
we can copy the resulting output from S3 to our local notebook instance,
将生成的输出从 S3 复制到本地 notebook 实例中
and then check to see how well the predictions did.
然后看看预测结果
Turns out not so bad. All right.
结果并不糟糕好的
So, now we're going to extend the mini-project in order to deploy it for the first time,
现在我们将扩展迷你项目并第一次部署它
much in the same way as we did with the Boston Housing notebook.
步骤和 Boston Housing notebook 中的基本一样
Of course deploying is relatively straightforward
当然 使用高阶方法部署相对较简单
using the high-level approach which is called the deploy method,
只需调用 deploy() 方法
and wait for SageMaker to setup our virtual machine and get it running.
并等待 SageMaker 设置和运行虚拟机
Now, that SageMaker has finished setting up
SageMaker 设置完
the virtual machine which we are using to deploy our model,
部署模型用到的虚拟机后
we can test the model again,
我们可以再次测试模型
we should get the same results that we got when we created a batch transform job.
结果应该与批量转换的结果一样
However, we're going to test it
但是我们将再次测试下
again to make sure that everything is working as we expect it to.
确保一切都按照预期运行
So, first in this case,
首先
because we're using the high-level approach,
因为我们采用高阶方法
we can use SageMaker's built-in serialization methods.
所以可以使用 SageMaker 的内置序列化方法
We just need to make sure that we tell SageMaker what
但是需要告诉 SageMaker
format our model expects to receive data in.
模型希望接收什么格式的数据
In this case, for an XGBoost model,
对于 XGBoost 模型来说
it expects CSV data.
应该是 CSV 数据
Now, since our testing data is too large to send in
如果在一次端点调用中发送所有的测试数据
a single invocation of our endpoint, we need to split it up.
则数据量太大 所以需要拆分数据
So, we split it up into chunks,
我们将数据拆分成一份份
and then we collect all of the output,
然后收集所有的输出
then we send our test data off to our end point to see what our model thinks.
将测试数据发送给端点 看看模型认为预测是什么
Now that our model has finished
模型对测试集
performing any predictions in it needs to on the test set,
完成所有预测后
we can take a look and see how well we did.
我们来看看结果如何
Good. We've got the same result as when we created a batch transform job.
不错结果与批转换作业的结果一样
Now, we deployed our model in this section,
我们在此部分部署了模型
so that we could test it to make sure that everything was working.
从而测试模型 看看一切是否正常
We're going to have to do a little more work before we can
在我们的简单网络应用中使用该端点之前
actually use our endpoint in our simple web app.
还有一些工作要完成
So, for now, we're going to shut down the endpoint that we've deployed.
暂时先关闭我们部署的端点
It's a good idea to do this,
要养成良好的习惯
if we're not going to use it in the near future,
因为如果暂时不用端点 则需要关闭
because remember that the cost of deploying an endpoint
因为部署端点的费用
is based on the length of time that it is running for.
按照运行时长计费
So, if you don't need it, shut it down.
不需要的话 就关了